The inbred hillbillies are back!
Wrong Turn 5: Bloodlines is a horror, thriller film directed by Declan O'Brien.
A small West Virginia town is hosting the legendary Mountain Man Festival on Halloween, where
throngs of costumed party goers gather for a wild night of music and mischief.
But an inbred family of hillbilly cannibals kill the fun when they trick and
treat themselves to a group of visiting college students.
Sheriff Angela, played by Camilla Arfwedson.
Maynard, played by Doug Bradley.
Linda, played by Borisa Tyutyundzhieva.
Lita, played by Roxanne McKee.
Gus, played by Paul Luebke.
Ginny, played by Rosie Holden.
Wrong Turn 5: Bloodlines (also known simply onscreen as Wrong Turn 5) is a
2012 slasher film written and directed by Declan O'Brien.
The film stars Doug Bradley, Camilla Arfwedson, Simon Ginty, Roxanne
McKee, Paul Luebke, Oliver Hoare, and Kyle Redmond Jones.
It is the fifth installment in the Wrong Turn film series, and is both a sequel to Wrong Turn 4:
Bloody Beginnings (2011), and the second part of the prequel to Wrong Turn (2003).
The film follows a group of college students, on a trip to the Mountain Man Festival
on Halloween in West Virginia, who encounter a clan of cannibals.
Wrong Turn 5: Bloodlines was released on DVD and Blu-ray on October 23, 2012.
Upon release, the film received largely negative reviews from critics and fans and is often considered the
worst sequel in the series, with many criticizing its characters, plot, poor CGI, and acting.
The film was followed by Wrong Turn 6: Last Resort (2014).
The film explores themes of small town, mutant,
halloween, forest, west virginia.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.